EFEOGHENE ANIEKAN OGODO

IT Service Desk Analyst

DETAILS

ADDRESS

10, Hemlock Close PE1 4FZ, Peterborough United Kingdom

PHONE

07780187742

EMAIL

riches49@gmail.com

DRIVING LICENCE

Full UK License

NATIONALITY

British

LINKS

github

<u>linkedin</u>

SKILLS

Project Management Skills

Customer Relations

Ability to Work in a Team

Analytical Thinking Skills

PROFILE

A highly skilled and experienced help desk specialist who has extensive knowledge of the IT help desk ticketing system and the help desk application. Results-oriented and adaptable **IT operations professional** with experience in customer service, technical support, PC maintenance, and system administration. Possess adeptness in implementing technology-based solutions for business problems, along with standards, procedures, and processes that improve business functionality.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Service Desk Analyst, CDW- UK

Peterborough

Jun 2022 — Present

- Providing customers with email and telephone support
 Consistently meeting call handling goals with a high first-call resolution rate.
- Troubleshooting a variety of hardware, software, and connectivity issues
- Manage all aspects of Microsoft Active Directory group policy, including creating and managing end-user accounts.
- · Provide end-user with information on available upgrading.
- · Virus removal by scanning with computer malware and opening the system through safe mode
- · Add a WiFi printer to the computer.
- · Troubleshooting IT issues by using remote desktop software.
- Creating, and tracking tickets through ServiceNow in accordance with SLAs.

Security Guard, Ogodo Services Ltd

Peterborough

Jun 2017 — Jun 2022

 Managed all documents and kept track of contractors' deliveries, and supplies with skills in Microsoft Word and excel spreadsheets.
 Communicating, via Microsoft Teams Strategic Planning

Ability to Multitask

Microsoft PowerPoint

Time Management

Complex Problem Solving

Project Management

LANGUAGES

English

- Operated handheld metal detectors and other surveillance devices to screen individuals entering the facility.
- Remained calm, assertive, and mindful to think critically and problem solve during stressful situations.
- Inspected and adjusted security systems, equipment, and machinery to maximize coverage of parking lots and building interior and exterior.
- Supported criminal investigations by collaborating fully with local law enforcement representatives.

EDUCATION

BSc (Hons) Computing and Information Systems, Anglia Ruskin University

Peterborough

Jan 2019 — Jul 2022

Access To HE:Information Systems And Business, Peterborough Regional Collage

Peterborough

Dec 2017 — Jun 2019

REFERENCES

References available upon request